This is the time known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates go to battle across the seas in search of the One Piece,
the legendary treasure left behind by Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned to rubber after eating the gum gum fruit,
set sail to become the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the unwanted attention of the world government,
which will use any means necessary to stop them.
Now this excites!
I can't wait to see what kind of adventure's up next!
With a charted course awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will cut a path across the Grand Line to the New World.
Luffy grieved over the loss of his brother Ace in the War of the Best against the Navy.
After recovering thanks to Jinbei's encouragement,
he met with Dark King Rayleigh.
Well then, that's it.
If you think I should, I'll go back.
To Marineford!
One by one, the rest of the Straw Hats learned of the big news.
No way! I don't believe it! Luffy!
Uh, Luffy.
Oh, good. He's safe.
It's in today's paper?
Whoa!
Unexpected Relanding! Luffy to Marineford!
At Navy Headquarters, located on the Grand Line.
It's incomprehensible!
During the War of the Best, it was revealed that Straw Hat is the late Portcastee Ace's adopted brother,
on top of also being the son of the Revolutionary Dragon,
which would make him the grandson of our own Vice Admiral Garp,
if you're paying attention.
So tell me, how did all of this slip past us?
After the war, he went missing, but lo and behold, he was alive as we expected.
Now, after everything that's happened, he has the call to come to Marineford again!
A few days ago?
The damage is unreal.
What did you expect?
It was an all-out war between the Navy elite and the world's greatest pirate.
It's a miracle that the island is still standing, isn't it?
So what brings you out to this pile of rubble?
A story, of course.
I came from Alabasta to cover Crocodile and Straw Hat.
Though, supposedly, Straw Hat could already be dead.
I'm sure the Navy wants you to think that,
but right now there's no way of knowing what with everything else that's going on.
I mean, look at what they're dealing with here.
That's true.
The One Piece!
The One Piece is real!
With his dying words, Whitebeard inspired pirates all over the world.
They're committing crimes more often than before.
Every able-bodied Navy soldier available has to deal with the increase in pirate activity.
Well, how unfortunate for them.
Huh.
Speaking of which, here come some Navy soldiers now.
Huh?
What's wrong with them?
How come they're still out there instead of jockeying?
Hey.
The ship is acting funny.
A blank shot?
What's going on?
Have they contacted us?
No, sir.
He came back?
But why?
Is that kid out of his mind?
Who came back?
Look!
It's Straw Hat Luffy!
You've got to be kidding me!
He must have stolen that ship!
He's out for revenge!
Pirates never learn.
Take the ship!
Fishman Jiu Jitsu Data begitu!
Where?
Fast and wild Lehrer is going to kill para acting as a manhain gateor.
Peggyan while humans Zhang fouled him with the car!
He disappeared!
What?
No, sir.
Let's haven't done anything...
I didn't have any guys.
I don't know through this.
No, seriously.
I don't know right out loud enough.
You know миним,
whenever he comes back to about beingful as many Tro非 robots.
That's why I got lost.
You know he came back.
It's Jin-Bang, that traitor!
There's someone else!
Uh-oh. This could get ugly, men.
They've got the first mate of the Roger Pirates with them!
Dark King Rayleigh!
Look! It still hasn't come any closer to the shore!
They circled around the island once. It's like a funeral at sea!
It's a taunt. Without our main forces here, they think they can bury us alive.
Enough! Barrage them from all directions!
Fire at will!
You've made it this far. Might as well get to work.
Right!
Don't let him get away!
If you want someone to fight, I'm ready and waiting!
Not too fancy to fight an old man, are you?
Come, come!
Ah!
What is Straw Hat doing?
It seems like he's looking for something.
That or he came back to bring the whole island down.
Yeah!
Ah!
He's up at the ox bell. What is he up to?
Gum-gum!
What is Straw Hat doing?
It seems like he's looking for something.
That or he came back to bring the whole island down.
He's up at the Oxbell. What is he up to?
What is he up to?
What's he up to?
What iszeitig Alanaяс義?
Looking
Flowers?
Now this is going to make for a great photo!
Don't let him get away!
And now he's leaving?
What was that all about?
Dark King Rayleigh? The Warlord Jimbe? Are they forming an alliance?
Rayleigh used to be a crew member of Gold Rogers.
Could Straw Hat be Roger's successor?
Straw Hat may be Ace's brother, but he's not Gold Rogers' son.
This whole thing is weird.
Wow, no matter how you spin it, this story is going to be huge!
This article's already been circulated throughout the entire world.
Those journalists are so starved for attention, they even mentioned how Straw Hat escaped.
This is humiliating!
If we take this appearance of his at face value, all Straw Hat did was pay tribute to his brother,
Ace, Whitebeard, and all the other people who died in the war.
The moment of silence and trip around Marine Ford support that notion.
But he rung the bell not twice as is customary.
But a whopping 16 times! 16 bell tolls!
There's no doubt in my mind that this is a challenge to us!
Oh, honestly, for such a rookie, this Straw Hat Luffy is certainly controversial.
But the boy is Garp's grandson, so I suppose I shouldn't be surprised.
I'm curious as to how he and Rayleigh know each other.
I highly doubt Rayleigh intended to rejoin the fray.
A pity Jinbei decided to turn against us.
His allegiance to the world government as a warlord acted as a symbol of inter-tribal peace.
It's disappointing to lose him.
Thanks to this turmoil, the three great powers are completely unbalanced.
Also, how should we take care of the vacancies among the seven warlords?
First, we need to observe what will unfold in the new world.
Relationships and hierarchies among pirates are sure to change.
We must take great care in ensuring we pick the most powerful ones.
Blackbeard already made his first move in the new world, by the way.
He knocked off a promising rookie, one that had a bounty of over 100 million berries.
And thanks to his time with Whitebeard, he knows all about the old man's territory.
He certainly has a lead over any other pirate who's aiming to become one of the four emperors.
No one else in history has ever eaten two devil fruits, yet he seems to have absorbed Whitebeards.
The only ones with the power to stop him are the other emperors.
Actually, perhaps Marco the Phoenix and the other Whitebeard survivors have a small chance as well.
It's always the D's who stir up the most trouble. First Roger, then Portgus.
And now, with Monkey D. Luffy, those names are exposed to the public far more than they should be.
I tried to talk him out of it, but as far as we're concerned, Garp is practically retired.
Though he does technically hold his title, so he's still a navy officer.
We need him to stay on board to train our young soldiers.
If you intend to resign from your position as Fleet Admiral, could you at least do that for us as well, Sengoku?
Yes, sir. I can accept that offer. It's not the worst way to spend retired life.
The two central figures who have led the navy since Roger's era are finally stepping down.
This will make quite a splash, I fear. Needless to say, you'll be missed.
Including the prisoners that were set free from the sixth level of Impel Down.
There's still a mess of dangerous pirates on the loose.
Before his death, Newgate was at the top of the list.
The great pirate era is in a period of transition.
Old navy officers shouldn't keep clinging to power.
The basis for justice changes from era to era.
It sounds like you're ready to step down.
Oh, Kong, while I'm here, I would like to recommend
Aokiji to take my place as the next Fleet Admiral.
He'd do a fine job.
They call this power Haki.
I'm certain that's what you've got.
Perhaps it was weakened by the trauma you experienced during the war.
Normally, the only way you could obtain the power of Haki is through vigorous training.
Haki? Are you sure, Doc?
You're pretty lucky, kid. It's the same power that the navy vice-admirals have in their possession.
Really?
I can feel all those people echoing in my head.
I can't make it stop.
You two are apprentices to Vice Admiral Garp, right?
Ask him about it.
Hey, Doctor! You think I might pick up some Haki too?
I doubt it.
It's not fair!
Damn it! We were partners and all of a sudden you're way cooler than me!
I don't know how to feel about all this.
But I do know how I feel.
Weird.
It's like I'm a completely different person.
But if this thing that happened to me really is Haki,
I might be able to use it to get stronger.
Much stronger than I am right now.
Maybe even as strong as him. For real this time.
I'm sorry, Admiral Kichi! We couldn't hold the fort!
It's fine.
Huh?
Alive after all.
Would you look at that?
You hear about Straw Hat going back to Marineford?
Crazy, kid.
Yeah.
The War of the Best is still fresh in everyone's minds,
and now Straw Hat rings the bell 16 times.
Is he trying to send some kind of message or what?
Beats me.
Anyway, did you ask them about my transfer?
Not yet, but I'll be sure to bring it up with Sengoku when I have the chance.
Are you serious about this?
Not really the sort of thing somebody would make a joke about, is it?
No, especially not you.
But either way, people aren't exactly clamoring to join G5.
I'm sure you've heard the stories.
It's not pretty.
So transferring to the fifth branch on the Grand Line, huh?
The new world.
You realize how wild things get over there.
For me, it's better to be closer to my target.
The news about Straw Hat Luffy quickly spread through countless waters.
Word even spread to the new world.
Straw Hat Luffy. Turns out the punk is still alive.
He rang the bell 16 times to mark a new era in Marineford.
So, what the hell is this Ox Bell thing?
A relic, you might say. It's a sacred bell from the Ox Lloyd.
A Navy warship that was quite impressive back in its day.
At year's end, they ring the bell eight times to signify the passing year.
Then eight more times as a sort of good omen for the coming year.
So that's the meaning of 16 rings. Some crusty old navy custom. Nothing special.
But since the year hasn't ended yet, maybe Straw Hat did it to announce the end and beginning of a new pirate era.
He came out of Marineford pretty cocky.
Whitebeard's era's over and he's acting like he's in charge of the next one.
Let the brat do what he wants. Everyone knows his brother's death hit him hard,
so he's gotta make a good showing before people think he's washed up.
He's gonna be a real pain in the ass.
His bounty's through the roof and it's only going up if he keeps pulling stunts like this.
Well, that's his plan, I'm sure.
Too bad. I'm gonna teach him the hard way that he can't do whatever he wants. Not here.
The new world.
From how they talked this place up, I thought it'd be more fun.
Not full of cowards like you.
What's the big idea, huh? Untie us right now. We didn't cause you any harm, did we?
This place is a living hell. We were trying to sail away. Please let us go back to paradise alive!
Paradise, huh? Do you mean your boring home that's pirate-free?
You just got here so you don't know how horrible the sea really is! Free us and leave while you can!
Straw head, huh?
Yes, father. He's cooking something up again.
No need to bother over that fool. If he keeps playing his cards so early, he'll burn out before
the end of the game. What is it?
Boss, come quick! It's the ship! It's not in the water! It's in the air!
What do you mean? What's going on? How's this possible? Control the ship, damage!
Look, bottom! Something is coming down from the sky!
Gah!
It's not coming down! We're going up!
Wait. Who are you?
I'm sorry. Could you say that again? I wasn't really listening to you.
I'm Brownbeard. There's a bounty of over 80 million berries on my head. Are you listening now?
This is my territory, so when you hear my name, you bow! You think you can sit your ass on my men and get
away with it? You gotta pay for that with your own blood.
I see. I thought I had misheard you because it's such a stupid name. I'll tell you two things.
Number one is I do not appreciate your jokes.
Is that so?
As for number two, I can see the shadow of death crawling upon your face.
And you're absolutely certain that's the island the log pose is pointing to?
Just look at it. It's raining lightning.
This isn't going to work.
How the hell do we get to the shore?
There is a realization that comes to all men who set foot in the new world.
Hey, priest! Somebody is approaching!
Huh? Who goes there?
All their struggles in the first half of the Grand Line suddenly seem petty.
Is that a young man waiting to greet me?
What do you want from us, old lady?
Because compared to this, those waters were like paradise.
Would you like an umbrella for your journey?
I'm telling you, if we stay here, we'll be dead! Every last one of us!
Let us sail back to paradise! I promise we won't get in your way! I beg you!
Man, this guy's a real wet blanket.
Didn't you choose the life of a pirate? You're not prepared to die for that.
Maybe you should have stayed away from the new world!
You want to throw down the gauntlet straw hat? That's fine.
But don't cry when I come for you, because it won't be pretty!
Luffy's latest incident in Marineford quickly becomes worldwide news.
Although his exploit was a success, it seems to cause little but bewilderment to all who hear it.
His strange message has met its target, but will his friends understand the next stage of his plan?
On the next One Piece! With hopes it will reach my friends!
Big news spreading fast! I'm gonna be king of the pirates!
But there is no persön 뭘 out of all locations here!
There's also an outlet in the Washington Post here that without any thought,
but that means I could double check!
At the second one, monkey or liberaterina!
Jacketでしょう?
There is an outlet in the lifetake of all these reactions,
so it's ayudar to fix.
It's time to fix it!